<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Existence on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/page/literature/existence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Existence on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:51:44 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/page/literature/existence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Orders on Earth</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/four-orders-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 09:34:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/four-orders-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>Upon seeing, four orders reveal themselves to the seer. Every order includes and is built upon the lower order.
 Material order - Ex. non living material units like atoms, stones, water etc. Innateness (Dharma) is to be/exist (with formation and deformation). Living (Pranic) order - Microbes, plants, animal and human bodies. Its Dharma is to be &amp;amp; to grow (i.e. respirate, metabolize, grow individually and propogate as species). Animal order - Self with animal body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Existence Itself Is Coexistence</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/existence-itself-is-coexistence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 13:54:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/existence-itself-is-coexistence/</guid>
      <description>Existence is all that is. All that is co-existing together is Existence. All is but one and only. Existence is inseparable, indivisible, absolute. Truth, knowledge, reality, actuality are different words meaning the same as Existence - all that is.
There is no &amp;lsquo;peer’ or other outside all that is (Existence). Can there be something left outside all that is?. There is no &amp;lsquo;creator&amp;rsquo; outside of Existence for where would the creator exist if not inside Existence?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 13:43:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/love/</guid>
      <description>What is love? Is attachment to someone love? Is being with someone to fill a gap within love? Is love conditional? We often say - “I love chicken or I love the color of your hair!”. Is that love? What is love?
If you have ever loved someone and don’t feel love today, did you ever love? If you expect to get love as a condition to give love, is it love that you are giving?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>