<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Literature on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/page/literature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Literature on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:51:44 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/page/literature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Space</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 12:47:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/space/</guid>
      <description>Space or Void or Shoony (Hindi)  Space is infinite energy in eternal equilibrium Because it is in permanent equilibrium, it is static; i.e. has no activity of its own.  It is transparent (does not affect any thing), omnipresent (present everywhere, even where there is no unit of Nature) and transcendental (is required for the units of Nature to coexist) Space is the (fundamental) field of which all fields, whether material or conscious, are part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Existence Is Coexistence</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/existence-is-coexistence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 12:42:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/existence-is-coexistence/</guid>
      <description>EXISTENCE (TRUTH)  Existence is all that exists (is). Existence is the only thing that exists. Existence is autonomous. Existence is indivisible, infinite, eternal, the ever &amp;ldquo;present&amp;rdquo;. Existence is as coexistence; of energy of two kinds - unmanifest and manifest Unmanifest energy can be called Space or Void or The field or Shoony (from Hindi/Sanskrit) Manifest energy can be called Nature or Prakruti (from Hindi/Sanskrit) Space and Nature have been called Father and Mother, Supreme Soul and Supreme Power, Shiva and Shakti, Omnipotence and Omnipowerful, Unmanifest and Manifest, Brahman and Prakruti, Shoony and Prakruti in different traditions Space</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction by Ayush</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/introduction-by-ayush/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 13:26:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/introduction-by-ayush/</guid>
      <description>My dear curious one
I have been waiting for you to arrive at this page. My name is Ayush and for the time being, I am the sole author of the essays listed below, touching upon the essence of Life, Existence and undivided, happy and prosperous Human Society. I have been through (a still ongoing) cosmic and very human journey of reunion with the source and in my inquisitive explorations have found universally acceptable answers (resolution) to some important questions pertaining to human existence on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Am I</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/who-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 14:20:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/who-am-i/</guid>
      <description>I am undivided being. I am eternal, infinite, omnipotent. I am inseparable, indivisible &amp;amp; all-that-is. I am Existence. I am eternal Existence experiencing itself as Life. I experience and express, always in the here and now. As Life, as an individual unit of Existence, I am aware and consciously experiencing the BIG ME (Existence itself). I am present here in the human form as a unique expression of the REAL ME.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>