<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/page/literature/lifemaker/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:51:44 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/page/literature/lifemaker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Proposal</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/about-the-proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 13:58:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/about-the-proposal/</guid>
      <description>In last few decades, an all encompassing, holistic perspective based on Existential reality as it is, has emerged. The proposals are (to be evolved if needed) such that they are naturally acceptable and self verifiable for every human alike, no matter what age, conditioning and background. The proposals promise to clear all doubts and misery when understood and imbibed.
Unlike most of previous human approaches based on faith before knowledge, these proposals encourage to assume (have faith in) only what is known and understood by oneself as reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Model</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/working-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 13:23:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/working-model/</guid>
      <description>Greatly inspired from Madhyastha Darshan among other perspectives
 The six dimensions of the social working model (how to be) The proposed working model covers six proposed dimensions for self-governed and self-sustainable families organised as grassroots based cooperatives and self help groups to co-exist in Universal orderliness across villages, neighborhoods, provinces, nations and united-humane-nation. These six dimensions broadly cover every aspect from human to nature, but can be expanded into a larger list by breaking individual dimensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self governance</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/self-governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/self-governance/</guid>
      <description>The structure and decision making of undivided human society  All changes to vision, constitution, policies, memberships, working decisions &amp;amp; problem resolutions shall be done with consensus from bottom up through fractal design based self governing setup. At every level of the fractal, not more than 10-12 people will be involved in making decisions, with full trust and go ahead by the levels below.
 A family is a group of upto around 10 people, and will choose one member to represent it in its neighborhood family group in which upto around 10 families will participate, as a larger family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Lifemaker</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/why-lifemaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:07:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/why-lifemaker/</guid>
      <description>Happiness is our true nature. Every Human wants to be happy. All prophets, relegions and philosophers have spoken the same truth in different ways. And yet Humanity has evaded the light of happiness somehow. Most of us are caught in a blind rush, desiring happiness from actions or objects but don&amp;rsquo;t know answers to the what, why and how with stability and clarity. We have not been told so far that for happiness to happen in continuity for any family it needs mental resolution, material abundance, mutual trust/confidence and all-round fulfillment in relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Values</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 12:55:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/values/</guid>
      <description>This is the founding ground for human union To agree on same values of Life is the stepping stone to coming together for a grand party on Earth as one couple, family, team or undivided human society for justful, truthful &amp;amp; successful co-existence as humans.
Here we identified and enlisted some 30 values which are seen in enlightened Human Living. The explanation of every value may be done in so many ways and words, yet the essence of each value is to be realised by the heart and understood by the mind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>