<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 11:39:19 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates December to April</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-dec-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 11:39:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-dec-april/</guid>
      <description>In last five months, a lot of positive development happened at the end of Lifemaker. Here is the gist of the same
Travelling and spread of the message We travelled across India and did few events on Lifemaker, introducing the concept. We recieved welcome response, and also some volunteer contribution. People asked how can we get more involved. For the same we need an online social network and also an on ground presense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approach</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 16:02:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/approach/</guid>
      <description>Treat family as the unit of society and basis for perpetuating Human seed and realisation  Enlightened families in peaceful and justful co-existence, is healthy and happy Humanity in continuity  Understanding of life/human/self, existence as co-existence and conduct of humaneness in an objective way  This is a must for living the humane way Curious families will go through Family education program and adopting the Value based living. We will do Existence based human centric contemplation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/background/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:07:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/background/</guid>
      <description>Happiness is our true nature. Every Human wants to be happy. All prophets, relegions and philosophers have spoken the same truth in different ways. And yet Humanity has evaded the light of happiness somehow. Most of us are caught in a blind rush, desiring happiness from actions or objects, forgetting that it is available to everyone all the time. We are doing things in order to be happy, and not as beings of happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>