<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 15:45:44 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Education Program: 2019 Summer</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/2019-summer-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 15:45:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/2019-summer-camp/</guid>
      <description>A holistic educational experience for the Self, couples, friends and families An opportunity to experience and understand what you are as a human, what existence is as co-existence, the way to co-exist happily and resolved as humans on Earth. We will explore a set of proposals together, understand what is meditation and stay meditative all day long in midst of all activities and inactivities.
4th April to mid June, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates from December 2018 - January, 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-jan-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 15:43:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-jan-2019/</guid>
      <description>Hello my dear ones
Here are the updates from last two months of action at Lifemaker.
 We successfully crowdfunded a movable film studio and started our outreach and awareness campaign with families in village Saalig actively.  We kickstarted the cottage industry experiment by making home made Gajak with Desi Ghee and selling it without additional generation of plastic, in village shop, local market and as well sending to some friends across India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates July Nov 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-july-nov-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 18:32:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-july-nov-2018/</guid>
      <description>A lot happened in these 5 months. The Good We undertood a lot more The core team at Lifemaker understood a lot more about the right approach to start this project. We learned that people do not like to talk about things. They want action. People don&amp;rsquo;t want lectures. They want to know what they can do right away to solve a problem or challenge they face. So our whole approach change from education first perspective to taking both the working model and education in parallel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May June 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/may-june-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 23:27:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/may-june-2018/</guid>
      <description>We conducted introduction to Lifemaker workshops in five villages in Dharamsala area and engaged with 50+ families. Out of them 10 families have shown interested in sincerely dedicating their life energy towards our incubation program. We are very happy to have these families join us. On 31st June we will have our first Dharamsala meetup. Special thanks to Shri Pavitar Kumar Chaudhary and Bhawesh Asgar from Madyasth Darshan family for joining us and helping facilitate the program and developing the content for going forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates December to April</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-dec-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 11:39:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-dec-april/</guid>
      <description>In last five months, a lot of positive development happened at the end of Lifemaker. Here is the gist of the same
Travelling and spread of the message We travelled across India and did few events on Lifemaker, introducing the concept. We recieved welcome response, and also some volunteer contribution. People asked how can we get more involved. For the same we need an online social network and also an on ground presense.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>