<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Premise on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/page/literature/premise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Premise on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:51:44 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/page/literature/premise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Only the whole of Self can realise the whole of Self</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/only-the-whole-of-self-can-realise-the-whole-of-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 22:13:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/only-the-whole-of-self-can-realise-the-whole-of-self/</guid>
      <description>A part can not realise the nature of the whole Just like 1 can never comprehend 2, the mind alone can not comprehend the nature of Self (or Life) because it is only a part of Life and not the whole of Life.
 There is something deeper than the mind - it is that part of the Self which is &amp;lsquo;experiencing&amp;rsquo; everything - the body, the world, the mind and even itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The apriori or causal Truth</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-apriori-or-causal-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-apriori-or-causal-truth/</guid>
      <description>That reality which exists independent of every conscious being or subjective perspective is being called the apriori Truth.
 As previously discussed there are as many truth sets as number of people, animals or conscious beings in existence. Now let me ask you to think about this - All conscious beings live in a reality which existed before we came into existence and will exist even if we did not exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The job of any truth set is to be useful</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-job-of-any-truth-set-is-to-be-useful/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 17:59:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-job-of-any-truth-set-is-to-be-useful/</guid>
      <description>Every individual holds only to that truth set which they percieve to be useful.
 Every person has universal and irrevocable right to hold on to their truth set. They must surely find their truth as useful to them else why would they follow it? The day a person discovers some part of their truth set to be not useful for their happiness or growth, they look for a better or truer truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 billion people. 7 billion truth-sets</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/7-billion-people.-7-billion-truth-sets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 17:36:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/7-billion-people.-7-billion-truth-sets/</guid>
      <description>Every person or animal holds their own truth set. Their truth set holds true in their world view. And all of these truth sets coexist in existence. Hence 7 billion people, 7 billion truth sets.
 Any truth set consists of two main components - faith and belief.
Faith is based on following Faith statements are followed based on reality assumed to hold true without self inquiry. Typically they are followed because someone held in high esteem by the person has spoken them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>