<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 12:15:26 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Funds</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 12:15:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/funds/</guid>
      <description>Lifemaker is a by and for humanity project. Our goal is taking Humanity to final stage of Evolution - realised collective consciousness and Value based sustainable Order. For this big task to be accomplished, we need not only hard work and mind share from many, but also material and resource support, including funds.
We need funds for these immediate goals
 Register a not-for-profit organisation Setup a space for education, sustainability and immersive co-living in Dharamsala, HP, India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forum</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 11:53:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</guid>
      <description>This feature will be up soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whoami</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 12:20:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:24:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</guid>
      <description>Three kinds of Lifemaker members While we are talking of members as individuals here, we are in reality rcruiting families! Families are our favorite target audience, because in togetherness is the living proof of the individual&amp;rsquo;s realisation and happiness. And also, most of us feel most comfortable and at home, with our families which provide us the nurturing environment to grow.
Elders (or Budhdhas) By elders we mean the Self realised souls, who shine forth with unblemished illumination of the Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events and workshops</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/events-and-workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 13:51:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/events-and-workshops/</guid>
      <description>We engage with curious people, via our local or remote family incubation program. You can reach out to us or apply anytime via the lifeline
Here is our calendar for the summer of 2018
 21st March - 28th March, Bijnor, Uttar Pradesh, India May - Informal workshops and meetings with local youth and couples, from Dharamsala area. June 1st - 12th - Dharamsala, Himachal Pradesh, India June 31st - Dharamsala Family gathering and pilot kickstart August - September - Italy and Europe visit and sharing December 25th - General meeting in Dharamsala to present the project to general audience from the neighboring villages/town and welcome members to join and start collaboration  If you curious and wish to explore more with us, please visit us or invite us to your place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:33:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:29:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Singularity - All is ONE. ONE is All. Like gold exists as the self same in all jewels (forms) and even without jewels, but the jewels have no existence without the Gold, what exists as the unchanging same in all that is, and also where there is none of that, is the Source of everything. Because that Source is eternal, omnipresent and unchanging, free from desires and ever fulfilled, it&amp;rsquo;s nature is happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faq</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:38:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</guid>
      <description>Who are the main people behind Lifemaker and what is the history? Ayush Ghai, a computer engineer from IIT Kanpur by training, software developer/architect and serial entrepreneur by profession, and a messenger and helper for humankind by heart. He is the heart of Lifemaker project. He is also the director and main stakeholder of Mindgrep Technologies. Setting aside a promising career in the corporate world, Ayush moved Mindgreo to Dharamsala in 2012 in order to satisfy his thirst for knowledge of Self &amp;amp; Existence and find eternal peace within.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reading</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</guid>
      <description>List of books, videos, blogs and other reading material</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>