<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 15:14:18 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 15:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/videos/</guid>
      <description>Call to the tribe: An intro to the concept made in 2017 [English] Every human is seeking happiness, mostly externally. Happiness can only be found when we are in sync with own true nature, and it reflects in fulfilment of our relationships with the world and with our own Self. The individuals are like small streams, which may or may not be able to make to the ocean alone. But together, our company of Truth can form a large river, which surely will reach the ocean of realised co-existential bliss; and there will be mutual wellbeing and happiness all along the way and for all our future generations to come on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayush</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/ayush/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 14:09:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/ayush/</guid>
      <description>Ayush Ghai, a philosopher, meditator, computer engineer from IIT Kanpur by training, software developer/architect and entrepreneur, a &amp;ldquo;human&amp;rdquo; human, is currently coordinating the work of this project. He is also the director and main stakeholder of Mindgrep Technologies which is like a for social cause IT company. Setting aside a promising career in the corporate world, Ayush moved Mindgreo to Dharamsala in 2012 in order to satisfy his thirst for knowledge of Self &amp;amp; Existence and find eternal peace within.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forum</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 11:53:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</guid>
      <description>This feature will be up soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whoami</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 12:20:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:24:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</guid>
      <description>Three kinds of Lifemaker members While we are talking of members as individuals here, we are in reality rcruiting families! Families are our favorite target audience, because in togetherness is the living proof of the individual&amp;rsquo;s realisation and happiness. And also, most of us feel most comfortable and at home, with our families which provide us the nurturing environment to grow.
Elders (or Budhdhas) By elders we mean the Self realised souls, who shine forth with unblemished illumination of the Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events and workshops</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/events-and-workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 13:51:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/events-and-workshops/</guid>
      <description>We engage with curious people, via our local or remote family incubation program. You can reach out to us or apply anytime via the lifeline
Calendar for 2019
 Summer camps between April and June 2019. Schedule and main website can be found here  Calendar for 2018
 21st March - 28th March, Bijnor, Uttar Pradesh, India May - Informal workshops and meetings with local youth and couples, from Dharamsala area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:33:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:29:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Singularity - All is ONE. ONE is All. Like gold exists as the self same in all jewels (forms) and even without jewels, but the jewels have no existence without the Gold, what exists as the unchanging same in all that is, and also where there is none of that, is the Source of everything. Because that Source is eternal, omnipresent and unchanging, free from desires and ever fulfilled, it&amp;rsquo;s nature is happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faq</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:38:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</guid>
      <description>What is the history of this movement? This vision of establishment of Undivided Human Society with a social order ensuring overall wellbeing for all, has been dream of many over time. In India, there have been a number of people who have been understanding, talking about and working on the proposal since many years. The good news is that now we seem to have a universally acceptable perspective and solution proposal, thanks to work done by some in 20th and 21st century, especially the Madhyastha Darshan movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reading</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</guid>
      <description>List of books, videos, blogs and other reading material</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>