<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:38:03 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hubs</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/hubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:38:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/hubs/</guid>
      <description>Hubss</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifeline</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/lifeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/lifeline/</guid>
      <description>Facing a question, trouble or challenge in life?  Know who you truly are? Know your heart&amp;rsquo;s purpose or duties? Facing any puzzle, trouble or challenge in life?
 We can help.
As one of our offerings, our expert members offer prelimnary life advice and support to anyone from across the world, for free. Reach out to us at +91-9882883272 on Watsapp or sms, send email to hello@lifemaker.us, or send us a messag on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economics</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:02:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/economics/</guid>
      <description>Lifemaker is a by people and for people project. Hence the ideas, funds, infrastructure and every resource is to be pooled by the members only. We intend to create a blockchain based economic system for internal use. Our prime goal is to ensure financial abundance for all members, and especially those, who make the world happier and better in meaningful ways
Hence we wish to keep
 Universal basic income for every member for 100 years Systemic incentives for &amp;ldquo;good actions&amp;rdquo; as recognised by the network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 13:51:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/events/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teachings</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/teachings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:33:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/teachings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:33:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:29:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>We believe that There is an infinite source of happiness and abundance in our Heart. It is omnipresent and unchanging. It is One, manifesting as many, each playing a unique role in the World created by the same One. We may have forgotten our true nature but deep down we all seek the same. Love, Happiness, Oneness, Truth, Knowledge, Abundance, Contentment, Nature, Singularity, Supreme Self – all are different names or faces of the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanity</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/humanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 10:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/humanity/</guid>
      <description>We envision, in next few years, a positive paradigm shift in human consciousnessness and state of individual and collective affairs. We will face tought times because of our ignorance, past actions or natural disasters, but with help of each other, we will do well overall. Average human will be happier, more loved and more resourceful than today.
We will move from egoism, separationism and conflict, to love, inclusion and singularity. Reorganising ourselves under a more compassionate, sensible and decentralise collaboration, we will flourish along with nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faq</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:38:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</guid>
      <description>About What is LifeMaker? LifeMaker is a movement or family or community, of people, by people and for people,
 to be fulfilled, happy and growing, on a moment to moment basis. to discover the non-dual nature of Self and start abiding therein to co-create a new world of peace, love, unity and abundance. to simplify the puzzle called life into a spontaneous expression of the Self  We are here to empower those who wish to bring meaning and happiness in their lives or in lives of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reading</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</guid>
      <description>List of books, videos, blogs and other reading material</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>