<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 16:02:06 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Approach</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 16:02:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/approach/</guid>
      <description>We are in discussions as an international group evolving the blueprint. Here is the latest status of this document
Our eight step approach  Meet with an open frame, to understand and See reality (Life, Living, Existence, Co-existence) as-it-is  Attend one of our introductory workshops of 7 days We will do Existence based human centric contemplation. It is an alternative to Materialism/Science and Theism/Spiritualism. It equips us with clarity for every dimension of our lives via realization knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/background/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:07:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/background/</guid>
      <description>We can all agree that happiness is the ultimate desire behind all desires and actions. We live lifetimes, doing things in order to be happy and to know our selves, hence feeling happiness in pieces and being in some kind of unease for rest of the time. Not knowing what we need exactly, we keep trying this and that. In process, we have hurt the Earth and each other to a great extent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Values</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 12:55:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/values/</guid>
      <description>You can read about our value system here or download a copy from here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forum</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 11:53:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</guid>
      <description>This feature will be up soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/model/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 13:07:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/model/</guid>
      <description>The family based approach consists of five main components.
 satsang - a mutually fulfilling environment providing nutrition, safety and love where every member feels trust and emotional wellbeing discussion - in Satsang, we mutually discuss how can wellbeing and safety be achieved in a jutsful way study - how to be and do, with happiness and not for happiness. How can this state of happiness change from being initially repetitive to ultimately continous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whoami</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 12:20:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:24:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</guid>
      <description>Three kinds of Lifemaker members While we are talking of members as individuals here, we are in reality rcruiting families! Families are our favorite target audience, because in togetherness is the living proof of the individual&amp;rsquo;s realisation and happiness. And also, most of us feel most comfortable and at home, with our families which provide us the nurturing environment to grow.
Elders (or Budhdhas) By elders we mean the Self realised souls, who shine forth with unblemished illumination of the Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economics</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:02:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/economics/</guid>
      <description>Lifemaker is a by people and for people project. Hence the ideas, funds, infrastructure and every resource is to be pooled by the members only. We intend to create a blockchain based economic system for internal use. Our prime goal is to ensure financial abundance for all members, and especially those, who make the world happier and better in meaningful ways
Hence we wish to keep
 Universal basic income for every member for 100 years Systemic incentives for &amp;ldquo;good actions&amp;rdquo; as recognised by the network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 13:51:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/workshops/</guid>
      <description>21st March - 28th March, Bijnor, Uttar Pradesh, India May and June ongoing - Dharamsala, Himachal Pradesh, India  If you curious and wish to explore more with us, you will have to visit us or invite us to your place, for a workshop/retreat of 7 days.
In our workshops we provide homely environment, nutritious food and comfortable stay. Ours is an environment of a safty, wellbeing and trust (Satsangha), discussions, study, contemplation and meditation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teachings</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/teachings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:33:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/teachings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:33:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:29:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Singularity - All is ONE. ONE is All. Like gold exists as the self same in all jewels (forms) and even without jewels, but the jewels have no existence without the Gold, what exists as the unchanging same in all that is, and also where there is none of that, is the Source of everything. Because that Source is eternal, omnipresent and unchanging, free from desires and ever fulfilled, it&amp;rsquo;s nature is happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faq</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:38:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</guid>
      <description>About Who are the people involved in this project? There are many people who’ve helped/inspired the LifeMaker project and have given an invaluable contribution to its inception. We are joined by a bunch of elders, volunteers and supporters in different roles. We are getting special help from Saadho and Enlightened Family Project teams.
Can I join? Everyone is welcome to join. Our tribe welcomes people from any walk of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifeline</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/lifeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/lifeline/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to reach out to us anytime, for anything  Our contact details are on the left side menu of your desktop screen or the hamburger menu of your phone screen.
 We will do the best we can, for you  Any problem you are facing Curious to explore an objective understanding of Existence and Co-existence as-it-is; and the solution to all our problems. Our group and their friends are experts in the areas of Self discovery, Self help, health, nutrition, holistic fitness, philosophy, meditation, enlightenment, happiness, relationships, leadership, entrepreneurship, communities, success, natural living, (low cost) travel, holistic education, skill-based empowerment, sustainability, permaculture and gardening, technology, internet, society, animals, environment etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reading</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</guid>
      <description>List of books, videos, blogs and other reading material</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>