<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 13:54:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Existence Itself Is Coexistence</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/existence-itself-is-coexistence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 13:54:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/existence-itself-is-coexistence/</guid>
      <description>What is existence? Existence is all-that-is. Existence itself is co-existence. Existence is inseparable, indivisible, absolute. Existence itself is truth, knowledge, reality, actuality.
Existence is one and only. There is no &amp;lsquo;peer’ or other outside existence. There is no &amp;lsquo;creator&amp;rsquo; outside of existence for where would the creator exist if not inside existence?
Existence itself is God. Existence is all there is to know. Existence is the total object of knowing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 13:43:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/love/</guid>
      <description>What is love? Is attachment to someone love? Is being with someone to fill a gap within love? Is love conditional? We often say - “I love chicken or I love the color of your hair!”. Is that love? What is love?
If you have ever loved someone and don’t feel love today, did you ever love? If you expect to get love as a condition to give love, is it love that you are giving?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May June 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/may-june-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 23:27:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/may-june-2018/</guid>
      <description>We conducted introduction to Lifemaker workshops in five villages in Dharamsala area and engaged with 50+ families. Out of them 10 families have shown interested in sincerely dedicating their life energy towards our incubation program. We are very happy to have these families join us. On 31st June we will have our first Dharamsala meetup. Special thanks to Shri Pavitar Kumar Chaudhary and Bhawesh Asgar from Madyasth Darshan family for joining us and helping facilitate the program and developing the content for going forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates December to April</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-dec-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 11:39:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-dec-april/</guid>
      <description>In last five months, a lot of positive development happened at the end of Lifemaker. Here is the gist of the same
Travelling and spread of the message We travelled across India and did few events on Lifemaker, introducing the concept. We recieved welcome response, and also some volunteer contribution. People asked how can we get more involved. For the same we need an online social network and also an on ground presense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funds</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 12:15:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/funds/</guid>
      <description>Lifemaker is a by and for humanity project. Our goal is taking Humanity to final stage of Evolution - realised collective consciousness and Value based sustainable Order. For this big task to be accomplished, we need not only hard work and mind share from many, but also material and resource support, including funds.
We need funds for these immediate goals
 Register a not-for-profit organisation Setup a space for education, sustainability and immersive co-living in Dharamsala, HP, India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Lifemaker</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/why-lifemaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:07:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/why-lifemaker/</guid>
      <description>Happiness is our true nature. Every Human wants to be happy. All prophets, relegions and philosophers have spoken the same truth in different ways. And yet Humanity has evaded the light of happiness somehow. Most of us are caught in a blind rush, desiring happiness from actions or objects but don&amp;rsquo;t know answers to the what, why and how with stability and clarity. We have not been told so far that for happiness to happen in continuity for any family it needs mental resolution, material abundance, mutual trust/confidence and all-round fulfillment in relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Values</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 12:55:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/values/</guid>
      <description>This is work in progress and is still in somewhat abstract shape. Here we identified and enlisted some 30 values which are seen in enlightened Human Living. You should expect improvements in time to come. Shall you feel like looking at the current draft, it is available for download here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forum</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 11:53:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</guid>
      <description>This feature will be up soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family education</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/family-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 13:07:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/family-education/</guid>
      <description>We believe family education is the way to educate our selves, and bring forth a new System and Order. By family, we mean at least two people committed to being together for Life, and growing with mutual fulfillment. Family is the fundamental social unit for mutual wellbeing; and safe and comfortable space for collective discussions, study, contemplation and meditation upon Life and Living. An integrated, enlightened and healthy family is the basic unit for an integrated, enlightened and healthy human society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whoami</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 12:20:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:24:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</guid>
      <description>Three kinds of Lifemaker members While we are talking of members as individuals here, we are in reality rcruiting families! Families are our favorite target audience, because in togetherness is the living proof of the individual&amp;rsquo;s realisation and happiness. And also, most of us feel most comfortable and at home, with our families which provide us the nurturing environment to grow.
Elders (or Budhdhas) By elders we mean the Self realised souls, who shine forth with unblemished illumination of the Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events and workshops</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/events-and-workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 13:51:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/events-and-workshops/</guid>
      <description>We engage with curious people, via our local or remote family incubation program. You can reach out to us or apply anytime via the lifeline
Here is our calendar for the summer of 2018
 21st March - 28th March, Bijnor, Uttar Pradesh, India May - Informal workshops and meetings with local youth and couples, from Dharamsala area. June 1st - 12th - Dharamsala, Himachal Pradesh, India June 31st - Dharamsala Family gathering and pilot kickstart August - September - Italy and Europe visit and sharing October - December - Dharmasala meetup, and workshops (dates to be declared soon)  If you curious and wish to explore more with us, please visit us or invite us to your place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:33:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:29:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Singularity - All is ONE. ONE is All. Like gold exists as the self same in all jewels (forms) and even without jewels, but the jewels have no existence without the Gold, what exists as the unchanging same in all that is, and also where there is none of that, is the Source of everything. Because that Source is eternal, omnipresent and unchanging, free from desires and ever fulfilled, it&amp;rsquo;s nature is happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faq</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:38:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</guid>
      <description>About Who are the people involved in this project? Primarily at the moment we are three couples and our friends and family support our vision. We are evolving a deeper understanding into self and everything together and we want to collaborate with our neighboring villagers and rest of humanity to bring forth the universal working model of Lifemaker as a timeless tradition across the world. Our team has a general track record of social service in some form or the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/</guid>
      <description>title: &amp;ldquo;Our approach in moving forward&amp;rdquo; date: 2018-03-17T16:02:06+05:30
draft: false  Treat family as the unit of society and basis for perpetuating Human seed and realisation  Enlightened families in peaceful and justful co-existence, is healthy and happy Humanity in continuity  Understanding of life/human/self, existence as co-existence and conduct of humaneness in an objective way  This is a must for living the humane way Curious families will go through Family education program and adopting the Value based living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reading</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</guid>
      <description>List of books, videos, blogs and other reading material</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>