<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Lifemaker</title>
    <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Lifemaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 19:13:08 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lifemaker.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposals</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/proposals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 19:13:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/proposals/</guid>
      <description>You can find some of the fundamental proposals in these lectures with QnA in this youtube playlist. Find more videos on our videos page
 Finally, thanks to collective work by many thinkers, researchers and realized humans, we have proposals for universal human resolution that should be able to solve for permanence, all human problems and needs - within each individual, family, village, area, nation, global human society and with rest of Nature - for as long as humans live on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approach</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 19:07:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/approach/</guid>
      <description>The approach In order to align together our only refuge is to understand universal reality and come together with that perspective to live together as &amp;ldquo;humans&amp;rdquo;. For this we need a parallel program for educational and societal reform over next 30 years. Here are the key points of the current proposed approach.
The team (Team formation currently in progress. Volunteers invited) A set of people who have understood well enough and are committed to the cause to constitute the working teams at different levels from international to national to village level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates 2019. Vision 2020. Volunteers needed.</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 13:38:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-2019/</guid>
      <description>Looking back upon 2019 News from the pilot village - Saalig, Dharamsala  Children from our Life Education and Excellence program have shown a remarkable change in their abilities and behavior. They like to ask questions, think, grasp the meaning behind words. They have an understanding on what really is the education that they need. They are letting go of their fears, challenging unverified assumptions and ensuring real knowledge within.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 15:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/videos/</guid>
      <description>[IMPORTANT] Introduction to the Proposals by an eminent teacher THIS YOUTUBE PLAYLIST has 8 lectures with some question and answers on each lecture.
A series of lectures, questions and answers giving holistic perspective on the nature of life as humans and the key to harmonious living. These videos were shot during one of his workshops at IIT Kanpur.
Global state of happiness and prosperity as of today [English]   Former Indian President, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Proposal</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/about-the-proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 13:58:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/about-the-proposal/</guid>
      <description>[IMPORTANT] Introduction to the Proposal by Prof. Ganesh Bagaria A series of lectures, questions and answers giving holistic perspective on the nature of life as humans and the key to harmonious living.
  In last few decades, an all encompassing, holistic perspective based on Existential reality as it is, has emerged. The proposals are (to be evolved if needed) such that they are naturally acceptable and self verifiable for every human alike, no matter what age, conditioning and background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Human Problem, need and opportunity</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-human-problem-need-and-opportunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 13:10:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-human-problem-need-and-opportunity/</guid>
      <description>The human problem  Our society and most of its individuals and families are not living freely, fearlessly, happily, harmoniously or mutually fulfilled, at least not all the time, if not most of the time.
 We are suffering from never ending strife, misunderstanding, miscommunication, division, conflict and misery at all scopes of human existence - within Self, families, neighborhoods, regions, humankind and with rest of Nature.
Till date humankind has not been able to establish a self sustaining, familial and social order and environment, such that it fosters continuity of true liberation, happiness and fulfillment within each individual, family and all its relationships - from physical family, to village, to neighborhood, region, state, to the World Family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayush</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/ayush/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 14:09:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/ayush/</guid>
      <description>Ayush Ghai, a philosopher, meditator, computer engineer from IIT Kanpur by training, software developer/architect and entrepreneur, a &amp;ldquo;human&amp;rdquo; human, is currently coordinating the work of this project. He is also the director and main stakeholder of Mindgrep Technologies which is like a for social cause IT company. Setting aside a promising career in the corporate world, Ayush moved Mindgreo to Dharamsala in 2012 in order to satisfy his thirst for knowledge of Self &amp;amp; Existence and find eternal peace within.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposals for nature of Self, Existence and Undivided Human Society</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/proposals-for-nature-of-self-existence-and-undivided-human-society/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 14:09:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/proposals-for-nature-of-self-existence-and-undivided-human-society/</guid>
      <description>The proposal Finally, we have a proposal that guarantees to solve all human problems and needs - within each individual, family, village, area, nation, global human society and with rest of Nature - for as long as humans live on Earth. The education arm of the social working model will present the same proposals to the society and help people internalize and experience the knowledge, in methods custom designed for children, youth and families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction by Ayush</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/introduction-by-ayush/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 13:26:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/introduction-by-ayush/</guid>
      <description>My dear curious one
I have been waiting for you to arrive at this page. My name is Ayush and for the time being, I am the sole author of the essays listed below, touching upon the essence of Life, Existence and undivided, happy and prosperous Human Society. I have been through (a still ongoing) cosmic and very human journey of reunion with the source and in my inquisitive explorations have found universally acceptable answers (resolution) to some important questions pertaining to human existence on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Model</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/working-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 13:23:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/working-model/</guid>
      <description>The six dimensions of the working model for self governance The proposed working model covers six proposed dimensions for self-governed and self-sustainable families organised as grassroots based cooperatives and self help groups to co-exist in Universal orderliness across villages, neighborhoods, provinces, nations and united-humane-nation. These six dimensions broadly cover every aspect from human to nature, but can be expanded into a larger list by breaking individual dimensions if need be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/family/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 13:20:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/family/</guid>
      <description>A relationship may or may not be related to the body, but it is accepted and fulfilled by the two minds.
 What is family? By using the word family, we are meaning - a group where every member trusts to find happiness in each other&amp;rsquo;s company.
A family is a group of people living together with assurance of mutual protection, fulfillment and love. It is the first place for a human to experience fulfilling relationships which nurture the body and self.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self governance</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/self-governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/self-governance/</guid>
      <description>The structure and decision making of undivided human society  All changes to vision, constitution, policies, memberships, working decisions &amp;amp; problem resolutions shall be done with consensus from bottom up through fractal design based self governing setup. At every level of the fractal, not more than 10-12 people will be involved in making decisions, with full trust and go ahead by the levels below.
 A family is a group of upto around 10 people, and will choose one member to represent it in its neighborhood family group in which upto around 10 families will participate, as a larger family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Education Program: 2019 Summer</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/2019-summer-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 15:45:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/2019-summer-camp/</guid>
      <description>A holistic and immersive educational experience for the Self, couples, friends and families 4th April to mid June, 2019. Participate in and experience symbiotic and joyful co-existence in nature, as human family An opportunity to experience your true Self as human and relation with rest of Existence, to find the source of lightness and joy within, to get answers to important questions, to understand own nature as well that of Existence and to experience and understand the only and universal way to co-exist happily and resolved as humans on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates from December 2018 - January, 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-jan-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 15:43:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-jan-2019/</guid>
      <description>Hello my dear ones
Here are the updates from last two months of action at Lifemaker.
 We successfully crowdfunded a movable film studio and started our outreach and awareness campaign with families in village Saalig actively.  We kickstarted the cottage industry experiment by making home made Gajak with Desi Ghee and selling it without additional generation of plastic, in village shop, local market and as well sending to some friends across India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humanity - a reality check from past to present. The good, the bad and the ugly</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/humanity---a-reality-check-from-past-to-present.-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 18:34:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/humanity---a-reality-check-from-past-to-present.-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</guid>
      <description>Past: 20th century AD and before Not so bad Humans were still learning and adapting to nature  More physical work to do. Less comfortable physical existence in terms of housing, clothing, heating, energy, health facility, food production etc. Higher mortality risk. Attack from animals. Climate. Weather. Diseases. Not such a developed surgery and medical system in west. But there was Ayurveda and chi gung in East. Uncleanliness and lack of hygene  The ugly Problems faced by humans between humans  Communalism and division between human to human Attack from each other - loot, crimes and war Ruled by power and fear - State, Religion Superstition also ruled the human mind  The good The good in the past  For every human the world was full of wonders to be discovered!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates July Nov 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-july-nov-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 18:32:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-july-nov-2018/</guid>
      <description>A lot happened in these 5 months. The Good We undertood a lot more The core team at Lifemaker understood a lot more about the right approach to start this project. We learned that people do not like to talk about things. They want action. People don&amp;rsquo;t want lectures. They want to know what they can do right away to solve a problem or challenge they face. So our whole approach change from education first perspective to taking both the working model and education in parallel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only the whole of Self can realise the whole of Self</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/only-the-whole-of-self-can-realise-the-whole-of-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 22:13:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/only-the-whole-of-self-can-realise-the-whole-of-self/</guid>
      <description>A part can not realise the nature of the whole Just like 1 can never comprehend 2, the mind alone can not comprehend the nature of Self (or Life) because it is only a part of Life and not the whole of Life.
 There is something deeper than the mind - it is that part of the Self which is &amp;lsquo;experiencing&amp;rsquo; everything - the body, the world, the mind and even itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Am I</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/who-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 14:20:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/who-am-i/</guid>
      <description>I am undivided being. I am eternal, infinite, omnipotent. I am inseparable, indivisible &amp;amp; all-that-is. I am Existence. I am eternal Existence experiencing itself as Life. I experience and express, always in the here and now. As Life, as an individual unit of Existence, I am aware and consciously experiencing the BIG ME (Existence itself). I am present here in the human form as a unique expression of the REAL ME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The apriori or causal Truth</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-apriori-or-causal-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-apriori-or-causal-truth/</guid>
      <description>That reality which exists independent of every conscious being or subjective perspective is being called the apriori Truth.
 As previously discussed there are as many truth sets as number of people, animals or conscious beings in existence. Now let me ask you to think about this - All conscious beings live in a reality which existed before we came into existence and will exist even if we did not exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The job of any truth set is to be useful</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-job-of-any-truth-set-is-to-be-useful/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 17:59:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/the-job-of-any-truth-set-is-to-be-useful/</guid>
      <description>Every individual holds only to that truth set which they percieve to be useful.
 Every person has universal and irrevocable right to hold on to their truth set. They must surely find their truth as useful to them else why would they follow it? The day a person discovers some part of their truth set to be not useful for their happiness or growth, they look for a better or truer truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 billion people. 7 billion truth-sets</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/7-billion-people.-7-billion-truth-sets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 17:36:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/7-billion-people.-7-billion-truth-sets/</guid>
      <description>Every person or animal holds their own truth set. Their truth set holds true in their world view. And all of these truth sets coexist in existence. Hence 7 billion people, 7 billion truth sets.
 Any truth set consists of two main components - faith and belief.
Faith is based on following Faith statements are followed based on reality assumed to hold true without self inquiry. Typically they are followed because someone held in high esteem by the person has spoken them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Existence Itself Is Coexistence</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/existence-itself-is-coexistence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 13:54:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/existence-itself-is-coexistence/</guid>
      <description>Existence is all that is. All that is co-existing together is Existence. All is but one and only. Existence is inseparable, indivisible, absolute. Truth, knowledge, reality, actuality are different words meaning the same as Existence - all that is.
There is no &amp;lsquo;peer’ or other outside all that is (Existence). Can there be something left outside all that is?. There is no &amp;lsquo;creator&amp;rsquo; outside of Existence for where would the creator exist if not inside Existence?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 13:43:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/love/</guid>
      <description>What is love? Is attachment to someone love? Is being with someone to fill a gap within love? Is love conditional? We often say - “I love chicken or I love the color of your hair!”. Is that love? What is love?
If you have ever loved someone and don’t feel love today, did you ever love? If you expect to get love as a condition to give love, is it love that you are giving?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May June 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/may-june-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 23:27:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/may-june-2018/</guid>
      <description>We conducted introduction to Lifemaker workshops in five villages in Dharamsala area and engaged with 50+ families. Out of them 10 families have shown interested in sincerely dedicating their life energy towards our incubation program. We are very happy to have these families join us. On 31st June we will have our first Dharamsala meetup. Special thanks to Shri Pavitar Kumar Chaudhary and Bhawesh Asgar from Madyasth Darshan family for joining us and helping facilitate the program and developing the content for going forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates December to April</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-dec-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 11:39:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/post/updates-dec-april/</guid>
      <description>In last five months, a lot of positive development happened at the end of Lifemaker. Here is the gist of the same
Travelling and spread of the message We travelled across India and did few events on Lifemaker, introducing the concept. We recieved welcome response, and also some volunteer contribution. People asked how can we get more involved. For the same we need an online social network and also an on ground presense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our approach in moving forward</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/our-approach-in-moving-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 16:02:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/our-approach-in-moving-forward/</guid>
      <description>Treat family as the unit of society and basis for perpetuating Human seed and realisation  Enlightened families in peaceful and justful co-existence, is healthy and happy Humanity in continuity  Understanding of life/human/self, existence as co-existence and conduct of humaneness in an objective way  This is a must for living the humane way Curious families will go through Family education program and adopting the Value based living. We will do Existence based human centric contemplation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Lifemaker</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/why-lifemaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:07:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/why-lifemaker/</guid>
      <description>Happiness is our true nature. Every Human wants to be happy. All prophets, relegions and philosophers have spoken the same truth in different ways. And yet Humanity has evaded the light of happiness somehow. Most of us are caught in a blind rush, desiring happiness from actions or objects but don&amp;rsquo;t know answers to the what, why and how with stability and clarity. We have not been told so far that for happiness to happen in continuity for any family it needs mental resolution, material abundance, mutual trust/confidence and all-round fulfillment in relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Values</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 12:55:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/values/</guid>
      <description>This is the founding ground for human union To agree on same values of Life is the stepping stone to coming together for a grand party on Earth as one couple, family, team or undivided human society for justful, truthful &amp;amp; successful co-existence as humans.
Here we identified and enlisted some 30 values which are seen in enlightened Human Living. The explanation of every value may be done in so many ways and words, yet the essence of each value is to be realised by the heart and understood by the mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forum</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 11:53:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/forum/</guid>
      <description>This feature will be up soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family education</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/family-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 13:07:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/family-education/</guid>
      <description>We believe family education is the way to educate our selves, and bring forth a new System and Order. By family, we mean at least two people committed to being together for Life, and growing with mutual fulfillment. Family is the fundamental social unit for mutual wellbeing; and safe and comfortable space for collective discussions, study, contemplation and meditation upon Life and Living. An integrated, enlightened and healthy family is the basic unit for an integrated, enlightened and healthy human society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whoami</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 12:20:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/whoami/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 21:24:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/members/</guid>
      <description>Three kinds of Lifemaker members While we are talking of members as individuals here, we are in reality rcruiting families! Families are our favorite target audience, because in togetherness is the living proof of the individual&amp;rsquo;s realisation and happiness. And also, most of us feel most comfortable and at home, with our families which provide us the nurturing environment to grow.
Elders (or Budhdhas) By elders we mean the Self realised souls, who shine forth with unblemished illumination of the Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events and workshops</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/events-and-workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 13:51:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/events-and-workshops/</guid>
      <description>We engage with curious people, via our local or remote family incubation program. You can reach out to us or apply anytime via the lifeline
Calendar for 2019
 Summer camps between April and June 2019. Schedule and main website can be found here  Calendar for 2018
 21st March - 28th March, Bijnor, Uttar Pradesh, India May - Informal workshops and meetings with local youth and couples, from Dharamsala area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:33:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/music/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:29:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Singularity - All is ONE. ONE is All. Like gold exists as the self same in all jewels (forms) and even without jewels, but the jewels have no existence without the Gold, what exists as the unchanging same in all that is, and also where there is none of that, is the Source of everything. Because that Source is eternal, omnipresent and unchanging, free from desires and ever fulfilled, it&amp;rsquo;s nature is happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faq</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:38:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/faq/</guid>
      <description>What is the history of this movement? This vision of establishment of Undivided Human Society with a social order ensuring overall wellbeing for all, has been dream of many over time. In India, there have been a number of people who have been understanding, talking about and working on the proposal since many years. The good news is that now we seem to have a universally acceptable perspective and solution proposal, thanks to work done by some in 20th and 21st century, especially the Madhyastha Darshan movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reading</title>
      <link>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lifemaker.us/reading/</guid>
      <description>List of books, videos, blogs and other reading material</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>